Hey, out of all of us
who do you think's going
to get married next?
Probably Monica
and Chandler.
Hi, could I have a pack
of Newport Lights, please?
Uh, we don't sell cigarettes,
but they have them
at the newsstand
across the street.
That'd be great. Thanks.
Oh, my God.
Melissa Warburton.
I don't think I have the energy
for this.
( theatrical gasp )
Oh, my God.
Ray-Ray Green?
( screaming )
Melissa!
( laughing )
You have been MIA
for the past seven
sorority newsletters.
What's up with you?
( laughing ):
Well...
Why don't I tell you over here?
So, last I heard,
you were going to get married.
Oh... poor Ray-Ray.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's good;
it's all good.
I actually work
at Ralph Lauren.
Shut up!
I will not.
I'm the Divisional Head
of Men's Sportswear.
Oh, shut up more!
Are you friends with Ralph?
Oh, please.
Are you?
No.
Listen
we-we have to have dinner.
What are you doing
tomorrow night?
Oh, tomorrow, I...
I don't know. Um...
You're having dinner
with me.
Shut up.
I've got to go.
This has been
so great, Ray-Ray.
Oh, there you are.
Um, so, listen,
just call me.
Here's my card.
Oh, wow, thanks.
Oh, you're in real estate.
Oh, no, that's...
that's an old card.
Um, I wanted to
get out of that
and do something
where I could
really help people
and make a difference.
Wow. So, what do you do now?
I'm a party planner.
I'll see
you tomorrow.
Okay.
Hey, guys,
look who's back.
It's Ray-Ray.
That was my friend Melissa
from college.
She seems really, really fun!
She's actually very sweet,
and we used to be very close.
Wait a minute.
She isn't... she's
not the one who you...?
Who you what? Who you what?
Yes.
Wow.
Wow-wow what? Wow what?
Who you what?!
Oh, it's not a big deal.
They were lovers.
What?
No, we weren't.
It was nothing.
It was one night senior year.
We went to a party...
had a lot of sangria,
and, you know, ended up...
kissing for a bit.
So, that's two of my wives.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Okay, so, this
is where the band is
and this is where the bar is,
and all these pins
have people's names on them.
Rach, here you are.
Oh, wow.
Well, why don't we
just take me
and put me
with a Manhattan in my hand
talking to the cute bartender?
( chuckling )
These pins aren't for playing,
are they?
Okay, the red ones are my guests
and the blue pins are yours.
This is so sad.
I mean, I only have,
like, ten pins.
Chandler, relax.
It's not a contest.
It's certainly not
a close one.
Hello.
Hey.
Hey, Rach.
Stop picturing it!
Okay, I think that's it.
The seating chart is done.
This is our wedding.
Wow. They all look like
they're having fun, don't they?
Hey, so, where are my parents
going to be?
Oh, let's see, well, if
this is the wedding hall
then, um, your
parents would be
over here at home in Queens.
What? They're not invited?
Oh, no, that's terrible.
They're going to be crushed.
Why would they think
they're invited?
You got me. I...
Joey...
Well, I'm sorry.
Look, I thought parents
were coming, you know?
Your parents are coming,
Chandler's parents are coming
Ross' parents are coming.
Ross' parents are my parents.
Well, see? Parents are coming.
You know, I think
we should invite them.
Oh, please.
You just want more blue pins.
Well, this is just sad.
All right,
all right.
Maybe I can
fit them in
if I just do some rearranging.
Now Rachel may actually have
to sit at the bar.
That is not a problem.
Maybe you'll order
a little sangria.
Oh, get out of here!
So, now, these are all
the tuxedos that we make
and if there's anything
that you like
we can make you a deal.
Anything at all.
But these are the three
that Monica pre-approved.
Ah, well, thanks a lot
for hooking me up, Rach
and I want you to know
that I want you
to attend our wedding
as my guest.
I'm Monica's
maid of honor, okay?
Don't try to blue-pin me.
Well, what's the deal
with these?
These look nice.
Oh, they are nice.
We, we custom-make
tuxedos for celebrities
and when they're
done with them
they send them back.
You mean, like,
for awards shows?
Some of them.
You mean these tuxes
have been
down the red carpet
with people yelling, uh
"Who are you wearing?
You look fabulous!"
Honey, might I
suggest watching
a little more ESPN
and a little less E?
Okay, who wore those?
Um... well, let's see.
Uh, this one's Tom Brokaw.
Not bad.
This one is, uh,
Paul O'Neill.
Who is that?
He plays for the Yankees.
Seriously, ESPN.
Just once in a while.
Have it on in the background.
Ooh, this one
was Pierce Brosnan.
Pierce Brosnan?
Uh-huh.
Are you serious? 007?
This is James Bond's tux?
Oh, I have to get married
in James Bond's tux.
It's a pretty cool tux.
Ah, it's not
just that.
I would be England's
most powerful weapon.
A jet-setting
heartbreaker
on Her Majesty's
Secret Service.
A man who fears no one,
with a license to kill.
Would Monica
let me wear this?
We should really learn
how to play the real way.
No, I like our way.
Oh...
Ooh, ah, hey.
Chess!
Nice move.
Yeah.
Hey.
So, Joey, I just hooked
Ross and Chandler up
with some tuxedos
for the wedding.
Do you need one?
No. I'm performing
the ceremony.
I'm not wearing a tux.
What are you going to wear?
Multi-colored robes.
Ooh, and maybe a hat.
Huh.
Does Monica know about this?
I don't think so.
Can I be there
when you tell her?
Hey, oh, Rach, wait.
Do you want to go
to a movie tonight?
I have to have dinner
with that Melissa girl.
Can I come?
I won't even talk.
You'll just hear the noise
from my video camera.
What is this?
What's going on?
Can I tell her, can I tell her?
Do you want to hear
what actually happened
or Joey's lewd version?
Joey's.
Okay.
No, hey, come on.
I have this friend from college
and I made the stupid mistake
of telling Joey
that one time...
she and I, you know...
kissed a little bit.
( chuckling )
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
It... it did.
Sure.
Hey, it happened.
Yeah, it was senior year
in college.
It was after the Sigma Chi luau
and Melissa and I
got very drunk
and we ended up kissing...
for several minutes.
Which means she had
a couple spritzers
and a quick peck on the cheek.
Why are you taking this
away from me?
Yeah, why is it
so hard for you to believe?
Okay, I just, I
didn't know that
you were lesbian.
I'm not saying
that I am a lesbian.
I'm just saying
that this happened.
Okay. It just
seems pretty wild
and you're, you
know, so... vanilla.
( muffled squeak )
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla.
I've done lots of crazy things.
I mean, I got drunk and married
in Vegas.
To Ross.
All right, you know what?
If you don't want to believe me
about this
why don't you just come with me
to dinner tonight
and she will tell you.
Okay.
All right, yeah.
'Cause I just can't picture it.
Oh, you should get
inside my head.
Hey.
Guess what I got
for your wedding?
A freakishly thin date
with a hanger for a head?
No, Rachel hooked me up
with a tux.
But not just any tux.
Batman's tux.
What?
That's right.
Made expressly for Val Kilmer
and worn by him
in the hit film...
that Batman film he was in.
You can't wear that.
I'm wearing the famous tux--
James Bond's tux.
So?
So, if you wear that,
it'll make mine less special.
You need something to
make this day special?
Hello. You have
the most special thing of all.
You are marrying
the woman you love.
( sarcastic gobbling )
Please don't take away
my cool thing.
Please? Pretty please?
"Pretty please?"
Not very, uh, 007.
Look, it's my wedding day, okay?
If you were getting married
I would never do anything
to upset you.
When I got married,
you slept with my sister.
That was pretty 007.
Hey.
Hey. Oh, good,
good, you're here.
All right, I
figured it out.
I'm going to take
two tables of eight.
I'm going to add
your parents.
And I'm going to turn
them into three tables
of six, okay?
Then I called
the caterer.
I added two extra meals.
We are good to go.
Yeah, they're
not coming.
What?!
Somehow,
they got the idea
that you only invited
them because of me.
They feel
a little unwanted.
Oh, that's too bad.
It's true.
But too bad.
Mon, if you could
just call my mom...
Oh, Joey.
Come on, look, just,
just to let her know
that you really want
them to be there.
Let's not forget,
this is a woman
who has sent you many lasagnas
over the years.
No, she hasn't.
Is it her fault
if some of them
didn't make it to you?
Well, what am
I going to say?
I don't know. Just...
just tell them there was
a mix-up
with the invitations.
Or... no, no, no.
Blame it on the post office.
They hate the post office.
And the Irish.
But I don't think you
can blame it on them, so...
Hello?
Yeah, hi, uh, Mrs. Tribbiani?
Hi, this is Monica Geller.
Yeah, I'm, I'm just calling
to say that Chandler and I
really hope
that you can make it
to the wedding.
Yeah, apparently a bunch
of the invitations that we sent
weren't delivered.
Um, I guess
there was some screw-up
at the damn post office.
Tell me about it!
Yeah, yeah, the
U.S. Post Office.
No, more like
U.S. Lost Office.
What are they, Irish?
Anyway,
his name's Alan
and we've been going out
for three years.
He was my first client
when I became a party planner.
Mmm!
He was actually planning a party
for his girlfriend at the time.
Oh, well!
Um...
And he was
Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse.
Oh, oh, that's great.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm, Phoebe, were you ever
in a sorority?
Of course, yeah.
I was a... a Thigh
Mega Tampon.
Uh... what one?
Yeah, you know, we
were really huge, too
but then they had
to shut us down
when Regina Filange died
of alcohol poisoning.
Oh, isn't it a shame
when one girl ruins it
for the whole bunch?
Mmm! Mm-hmm.
Mmm. Oh!
Anyway...
speaking of drinking too much...
I was telling, uh,
telling Phoebe
about that one
crazy night after
the Sigma Chi luau
where you and I, uh...
we made out.
What?
Remember, we...?
Come on, we both--
We had the sarongs
on and we had the
coconut bikini tops.
Yeah...
We went back to the house,
and we got really silly.
Then we... we made out.
Oh, wow.
Ray-Ray, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Really!
Ross is Batman.
Well, he did manage
to keep his identity secret
for a long time.
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo
that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
Okay, Batman is so much cooler
than James Bond.
What are you
talking about?
007 has all those gadgets.
Batman has
a utility belt.
007 has a fancy car.
Batman has
the Batmobile.
007 gets all the ladies.
Batman has Robin.
We get ESPN, right?
How about you go put on
your 007 tuxedo
and I'll make you
a nice martini?
Actually,
I don't like martinis.
Well, how about a Yoo-Hoo
with the funny straw?
Ooh, yum!
Hey.
Listen, I know
the invitation says 6:00
but does that mean
you want people
to get there
at 6:00, or the show's going
to start right at 6:00?
"The show"?
Right.
The wedding. Gotcha.
But, I mean, it's going
to start a little late, right?
I mean, weddings
start late, right?
Have you ever been
to one of my weddings?
Ah, yeah, well, look--
the thing is, is
it's the same day
as my niece's christening
and I really want my parents
to be there in time to see me
'cause my part's
just in the beginning.
I'm not even in the rest
of the show-- wedding.
The wedding starts at 6:00.
Okay, okay, I totally hear you.
Ooh! How about this?
I vamp a little
till they get there?
You'll "vamp"?!
Yeah, yeah, you know
like, warm up the crowd,
ask them where they're from
'cause in Joey Tribbiani
you get a minister
and you get an entertainer.
I'm a "minis-tainer."
All right?
( rapping ):
There's no one better.
There's no one greater.
Huh?
How can you not
remember us kissing?
I don't know.
I don't remember a lot of things
that never happened.
But...
Come on,
remember?
We were on the sleeping porch.
We couldn't stop giggling.
And our coconuts kept knocking
together.
Oh, somewhere,
Joey's head is exploding.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I don't want to make
you uncomfortable
but I told Phoebe that
it happened and she
doesn't believe me.
I'm sorry, Ray-Ray.
I mean, if I thought
it happened, I would say it.
Maybe I passed out
and you did stuff to me
while I was sleeping.
No!
Rachel, it's okay.
You don't have to do this,
all right?
I believe you.
Okay, if you say
that you kissed Melissa
then you kissed Melissa.
Thank you, Phoebe.
Okay.
But she didn't.
No, I know.
Hey.
CHANDLER:
Do you just
carry that around?
Yes, I find it to be something
of a conversation piece.
Between you and...?
Gunther.
Hey, hey.
Why don't we put them on?
You know, get a picture
of Batman
and James Bond together.
I would,
but mine doesn't fit.
The pants are
a little tight.
A little tight?
I could see double-O
and seven in those things.
Well, that stinks.
I was looking forward to us
wearing our celebrity tuxes
together.
Does that mean
you're not wearing yours?
What, are you kidding?
It's Batman's tux!
Let me try it on.
Okay,
but just the jacket.
Double-O and seven
are not getting in there.
Okay.
Holy double-vented comfort,
Batman.
What's this?
Huh?
An invitation
to the At First Sightpremier?
Oh, my God.
Val Kilmer didn't wear
this in Batman.
He wore it to the premier
of some tutti-fruitti love story
where he played a blind guy.
What? Let me see that.
Oh, man!
The only superpower
you have
is a slightly heightened
sense of smell.
Hey, uh...
Monica, Chandler
can I talk to you guys
for a sec?
All right, that's it.
I give up.
Whatever you want,
you can have it.
You want to sing a song
you want to do a dance
you want your mom to stand
at the altar
and scream racial slurs?
I don't care.
No, no.
I-I just wanted
to thank you guys
for what you did for my parents.
That was really sweet.
They're so happy they get to be
a part of your special day.
Oh.
Well,
you're welcome.
And tell them
we're really glad
they're coming.
Okay, I will.
Oh! Check out what they got me
to wear for the ceremony.
Huh?
I'll wear it like this
when I marry you guys
and then this is for party time.
It happened.
I am telling you,
it happened.
PHOEBE:
Okay.
Well, it was great meeting you.
And, uh, Rachel, I don't think
I'll be calling you
because, um, you know,
you've gotten weird.
MELISSA:
Um...
Take care, you guys.
W-Wait a minute!
No! Wait a minute.
Okay, look-- that night
was the one wild thing
I have ever done
in my entire life.
and I'm not going to let
you take that away from me.
Okay, so if you
don't remember that
maybe you will
remember this.
Oh, my God!
You love me.
What?
Of course
I remember our kiss.
I think about it
all the time.
I can still hear the coconuts
knocking together, I...
I just didn't want
to tell you
'cause I didn't think
you'd return my love.
And now that
you have, I...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, look who's being
suddenly shy!
You can't tell me
you don't feel
what I feel.
Nobody can kiss that good
and not mean it.
I'm, I'm, I'm just,
I'm just a good kisser.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you don't
have to be sorry.
I'm...
I'm obviously kidding.
I'm not in love
with you.
with her, I...
I don't...
hear coconuts
banging together.
You know,
I don't picture your face
when I make love
to my boyfriend.
Anyway, I've got to go.
Kiss good-bye?
No? Okay.
Wow... I mean
I had no idea that that was...
What the hell was that?
I just wanted to
see what all the
fuss was about.
And?
I've had better.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
CHANDLER:
I found one that fits.
Well, you know
what they say:
Twenty-third time's a charm.
( door opens )
Oh...
Look at you, all handsome.
Whose is it?
Oh, does it matter?
All that matters
is that you look so handsome.
Whose is it?
I don't want to say.
Oh, come on, I don't care.
Come on, whose is it?
Diane Keaton.